# **Beverley A. Fricker CV**

Junior Front End Developer in Amsterdam

contact@beverley-ann.com | beverley-ann.com

## Personal Profile

With experience in HTML & CSS, as well as my rapidly expanding skills in JavaScript & jQuery, I am at your disposal. As a frequent user of Bootstrap, I enjoy creating responsive UX solutions. I want to continue learning new languages and further develop my existing skills.

# Tech Summary

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap

- JavascriptiOuerv
- GIMP

- Corel Paint Shop
- Responsive Web design
- UX

# Experience

### RB, Hygiene, R&D Associate

January 2017 - March 2017

In this promotion I have gained more autonomy in my work, by taking on extra responsibility for my projects, while retaining all my previous roles.

#### **RB, Hygiene, R&D Assistant**

July 2015 - December 2016

A wide ranging role, focused on new product development, for the global brands of *Veet* and *Dettol*. Projects can involve working on anything from electrical devices with apps to cosmetics. My responsibilities include

- Formulation of personal care products
- IP Searches
- Project management
- Test method development

- Working closely with the app development, creating wireframes and user journey
- Training colleagues
- Working in a cross functional team

#### Extra roles:

- Departmental Health and Safety Representative IOSH Managing Safely Qualified
- First aider First Aid at Work (Level 1 Qualified)
- Fire Marshal In house training (Passed)

#### AkzoNobel, Yacht Antifoulings, R&D Intern

July 2013 - July 2014

While working on new and existing product development for the brand *International Paint*, I developed my knowledge of coatings and formulation. My responsibilities included:

- Formulations of Coatings
- Product testing
- Stability testing

- Studying paint phenomena
- Test method development and implementation

# **Beverley A. Fricker**

## Education

BSc (2:1 Hons) Chemistry with a Year in Industry, University of Sheffield September 2011 – July 2015

A combination of theoretical teaching, paired with practical applications of Chemistry. My final year projects were an in depth literature review 'The synthesis of 2,2- disubstituted tetrahydroquinolines' and a group computational research project 'Modelling the electronic structures of conjugated n systems in two and three dimensions using Hückel Theory'. One module involved creating a website (HTML & CSS) on the history and synthesis of Ibuprofen.

# **Interests**

Since 2012, I have played Rugby Union for 3 teams and held multiple committee roles, including captain. I particularly like the teamwork, sportsmanship and discipline of the game.

I am passionate about travelling and learning about new places and cultures. My journeys so far have taken me to Canada, Italy and Norway among others.

### Additional information

Proficient in the Microsoft Office Suite and LibreOffice Driving licence
RFU Licensed Level 2 Rugby Union Coach

# References

Available on request